Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Committee on Trusteeship, 1857 -- 2020; UA003.007; 4.7 Linear Feet; 17 Digital Object(s) 17 zip files containing 501 files.; 560.43 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, February 15, 1994; UA003.007.103.00001 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, September 30, 1994; UA003.007.103.00002 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, March 7, 1995; UA003.007.103.00003 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, August 22, 1995; UA003.007.103.00004 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1902 -- 1996; UA003.007.103.00005 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1903 -- 1996; UA003.007.103.00006 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1909 -- 1996; UA003.007.103.00007 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1901 -- 1997; UA003.007.103.00008 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1903 -- 1997; UA003.007.103.00009 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1905 -- 1997; UA003.007.103.00010 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1908 -- 1997; UA003.007.103.00011 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1903 -- 1998; UA003.007.103.00012 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1908 -- 1998; UA003.007.103.00013 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1903 -- 1999; UA003.007.103.00014 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 1908 -- 1999; UA003.007.103.00015 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 2000 -- 2005; UA003.007.103.00016 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship, Working Papers, 2000 -- 2009; UA003.007.103.00017 (Box 103)
  - Committee on Trusteeship Working Papers, 2006 -- 2010; UA003.007.130; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 130, Folder 26 - 36)
  - Committee on trusteeship files, 1998-2016; UA003.007.00001; 345 Digital Object(s); 0.43 Gigabytes
  - Committee on trusteeship files, 2016; UA003.007.00002; 13 Digital Object(s); .007 Gigabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2017; UA003.007.00003; 4 Digital Object(s); 3.07 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2017; UA003.007.00004; 10 Digital Object(s); 6.89 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2017; UA003.007.00005; 12 Digital Object(s); 7.68 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2018; UA003.007.00006; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.74 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2017-09-27; UA003.007.00007; 12 Digital Object(s); 7.7 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2018-07-13; UA003.007.00008; 10 Digital Object(s); 7.72 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2018-09-11; UA003.007.00009; 11 Digital Object(s); 6.89 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2019-02-07; UA003.007.00010; 6 Digital Object(s); 4.66 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2019-04-23; UA003.007.00011; 9 Digital Object(s); 7.17 Megabytes
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2019 September 17; UA003.002339; 14 Megabytes 18 files
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, ballot vote, 2019 September 26; UA003.002340; 4.3 Megabytes 6 files
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2020 June 09; UA003.002405; 10.87 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 13 files.
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2020 October 02; UA003.002406; 11.52 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 18 files.
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2020 November 30; UA003.002407; 1.62 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Committee on Trusteeship files, 2020 December 08; UA003.002408; 16.42 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
- University Advancement Committee, 1975 -- 2020; UA003.008; 2.4 Linear Feet; 12 Digital Object(s) 12 zip files containing 238 files.; 356.15 Megabytes
  This series contains material from Tufts University's University Advancement Committee from 1975 to 2000. The name of the Committee has varied between "Development" and "Resources" Committee, and is currently called "University Advancement Committee." These materials are arranged in chronological order by committee meeting date. Folders contain announcements, agendas, minutes, memos, and policies.
  An ad hoc Committee on Development was created in 1957 as part of a major fundraising effort (The Tufts University Program). It was made a standing committee in 1959. The committee's function is to strengthen the financial resources of the institution.
  - Development Committee, Tuesday May 6, 1975; UA003.008.049.00001 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 25, 1975/January 28, 1975 -- 1976; UA003.008.049.00002 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, September 21, 1978; UA003.008.049.00003 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, December 8, 1978; UA003.008.049.00004 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, March 14, 1979; UA003.008.049.00005 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, Thursday September 20, 1979; UA003.008.049.00006 (Box 49)
  - Resource Committee, Friday, November 2, 1979; UA003.008.049.00007 (Box 49)
  - Resource/Development Meeting, December 6, 1979; UA003.008.049.00008 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, January 31, 1980; UA003.008.049.00009 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, March 20, 1980; UA003.008.049.00010 (Box 49)
  - Resources Committee, Thursday, April 17, 1980; UA003.008.049.00011 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 24, 1980; UA003.008.049.00012 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, September 12, 1980; UA003.008.049.00013 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, December 5, 1980; UA003.008.049.00014 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, January 12, 1981; UA003.008.049.00015 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 27, 1981; UA003.008.049.00016 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 29, 1981; UA003.008.049.00017 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, October 23, 1981; UA003.008.049.00018 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 28, 1982; UA003.008.049.00019 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 25, 1983; UA003.008.049.00020 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 4, 1983; UA003.008.049.00021 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 8, 1984; UA003.008.049.00022 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 24, 1984; UA003.008.049.00023 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 18, 1984; UA003.008.049.00024 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 2, 1984; UA003.008.049.00025 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 2, 1984; UA003.008.049.00026 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 17, 1985; UA003.008.049.00027 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 27, 1985; UA003.008.049.00028 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 20, 1986; UA003.008.049.00029 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 16, 1986; UA003.008.049.00030 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 4, 1986; UA003.008.049.00031 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 8, 1986; UA003.008.049.00032 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 25, 1987; UA003.008.049.00033 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 15, 1987; UA003.008.049.00034 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 15, 1987; UA003.008.049.00035 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 13, 1987; UA003.008.049.00036 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 13, 1987; UA003.008.049.00037 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 26, 1988; UA003.008.049.00038 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 20, 1988; UA003.008.049.00039 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 4, 1988; UA003.008.049.00040 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 24, 1989; UA003.008.049.00041 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 19, 1989; UA003.008.049.00042 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 3, 1989; UA003.008.049.00043 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 3, 1990; UA003.008.049.00044 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 18, 1990; UA003.008.049.00045 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee,November 2, 1990; UA003.008.049.00046 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 22, 1991; UA003.008.049.00047 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 10, 1991; UA003.008.049.00048 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 1, 1991; UA003.008.049.00049 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 28, 1992; UA003.008.049.00050 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, May 15, 1992; UA003.008.049.00051 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, November 6, 1992; UA003.008.049.00052 (Box 49)
  - Development Committee, February 26, 1993; UA003.008.095.00001 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 21, 1993; UA003.008.095.00002 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, November 5, 1993; UA003.008.095.00003 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, February 25, 1994; UA003.008.095.00004 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 20, 1994; UA003.008.095.00005 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, November 4, 1994; UA003.008.095.00006 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, February 10, 1995; UA003.008.095.00007 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 19, 1995; UA003.008.095.00008 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, November 3, 1995; UA003.008.095.00009 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, February 9, 1996; UA003.008.095.00010 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 17, 1996; UA003.008.095.00011 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, November 1, 1996; UA003.008.095.00012 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, February 7, 1997; UA003.008.095.00013 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 16, 1997; UA003.008.095.00014 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, November 7, 1997; UA003.008.095.00015 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, February 6, 1998; UA003.008.095.00016 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 15, 1998; UA003.008.095.00017 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, November 6, 1998; UA003.008.095.00018 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, February 5, 1999; UA003.008.095.00019 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 21, 1999; UA003.008.095.00020 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, October 5, 1999; UA003.008.095.00021 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, February 11, 2000; UA003.008.095.00022 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, May 19, 2000; UA003.008.095.00023 (Box 95)
  - Development Committee, November 3, 2000; UA003.008.095.00024 (Box 95)
  - University Advancement working papers, 2006 -- 2010; UA003.008.129; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 129, Folder 1 - 15)
  - Committee for university advancement files, 2000-2016; UA003.008.00001; 121 Digital Object(s); 0.22 Gigabytes
  - Committee for University Advancement files, 2016; UA003.008.00002; 12 Digital Object(s); .013 Gigabytes
  - University Advancement committee files, 2017; UA003.008.00003; 6 Digital Object(s); 4.69 Megabytes
  - University Advancement committee files, 2017; UA003.008.00004; 14 Digital Object(s); 15.4 Megabytes
  - University Advancement committee files, 2017; UA003.008.00005; 11 Digital Object(s); 19.3 Megabytes
  - University Advancement committee files, 2018; UA003.008.00006; 19 Digital Object(s); 19.7 Megabytes
  - University Advancement committee files, 2018; UA003.008.00007; 13 Digital Object(s); 22.9 Megabytes
  - Committee for University Advancement files, 2020 February 07; UA003.002409; 14.09 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Committee for University Advancement files, 2020 March 27; UA003.002410; 1.46 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
  - Committee for University Advancement files, 2020 May 15; UA003.002413; 8.53 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Committee for University Advancement files, 2020 October 14; UA003.002411; 5.38 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
  - Committee for University Advancement files, 2020 November 06; UA003.002412; 11.69 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 12 files.
- Compensation Committee, 1977 -- 2019; UA003.009; 0.25 Linear Feet; 20 Digital Object(s) 20 zip files containing 188 files; .18 Gigabytes
  This series contains material from Tufts University's Compensation Committee from 1994 and 1997. These materials are arranged in chronological order by committee meeting date. Folders contain announcements, agendas, minutes, and memoranda.
  - Compensation Committee, 1977; UA003.009.099.00001 (Box 99)
  - Compensation Committee, Working Papers, 1994; UA003.009.099.00002 (Box 99)
  - Compensation Committee, 1997; UA003.009.099.00003 (Box 99)
  - Compensation Committee working papers, 2009 -- 2012; UA003.009.130; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 130, Folder 20 - 25)
  - Compensation committee files, 2009-2016; UA003.009.00001; 24 Digital Object(s); 0.06 Gigabytes
  - Compensation committee files, 2017; UA003.009.00002; 11 Digital Object(s); 6.73 Megabytes
  - Compensation committee files, 2017; UA003.009.00003; 11 Digital Object(s); 6.91 Megabytes
  - Compensation committee files, 2017; UA003.009.00004; 6 Digital Object(s); 6.05 Megabytes
  - Compensation committee files, 2017; UA003.009.00005; 6 Digital Object(s); 4.9 Megabytes
  - Compensation committee files, 2018; UA003.009.00006; 8 Digital Object(s); 4.66 Megabytes
  - Compensation committee files, 2018; UA003.009.00007; 15 Digital Object(s); 11.5 Megabytes
  - Compensation committee files, 2018; UA003.009.00008; 11 Digital Object(s); 6.48 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2018-07-03; UA003.009.00009; 8 Digital Object(s); 5.38 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2018-07-26; UA003.009.00010; 7 Digital Object(s); 3.93 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2018-11-13; UA003.009.00011; 7 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-01-18; UA003.009.00012; 8 Digital Object(s); 8.15 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-03-08; UA003.009.00013; 8 Digital Object(s); 4.91 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-04-01; UA003.009.00014; 8 Digital Object(s); 5.31 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-05-01; UA003.009.00015; 7 Digital Object(s); 4.79 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-05-13; UA003.009.00016; 8 Digital Object(s); 5.63 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, 2019-06-10; UA003.009.00017; 10 Digital Object(s); 7.48 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-06-26; UA003.009.00018; 8 Digital Object(s); 5.7 Megabytes
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019 October 10; UA003.002328; 7.3 Megabytes 8 files
  - Compensation Committee files, ballot vote, 2019 November 25; UA003.002329; 7.7 Megabytes 9 files
- Subcommittee Buildings and Grounds, 1960 -- 2020; UA003.010; 1.2 Linear Feet; 20 Digital Object(s) 20 zip files containing 501 files.; .89 Gigabytes
  This series contains materials from Tufts University' Buildings and Grounds Subcommittee from 1961 to 1980. These materials are arranged in chronological order by committee meeting date. Folders contain announcements, agendas, minutes, and memoranda.
  - Committee On Naming New Buildings, 1960 -- 1965; UA003.010.089.00001 (Box 89)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, working papers, May 8, 1980; UA003.010.089.00002 (Box 89)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, working papers, June 19, 1980; UA003.010.089.00003 (Box 89)
  - Buildings and Grounds Subcommittee, meeting minutes, November 9, 1962- September 24, 1981, Book 1 (Part 1), 1962 -- 1981; UA003.010.089.00004 (Box 89)
  - Buildings and Grounds Subcommittee, meeting minutes, November 9, 1962- September 24, 1981, Book 1 (Part 2), 1962 -- 1981; UA003.010.089.00005 (Box 89)
  - Buildings and Grounds Subcommittee, meeting minutes, November 9, 1962- September 24, 1981, Book 1 (Part 3), 1962 -- 1981; UA003.010.089.00006 (Box 89)
  - Buildings and Grounds working papers, 2005 -- 2009; UA003.010.128; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 128, Folder 1 - 28)
  - Buildings and Grounds working papers, 2009 -- 2010; UA003.010.129; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 129, Folder 26 - 32)
  - Buildings and grounds files, 2005-2016; UA003.010.00001; 292 Digital Object(s); 0.51 Gigabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2016; UA003.010.00002; 18 Digital Object(s); 55.1 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2017; UA003.010.00003; 14 Digital Object(s); 26.7 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2017; UA003.010.00004; 6 Digital Object(s); 16.8 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2017; UA003.010.00005; 14 Digital Object(s); 39.8 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2017; UA003.010.00006; 12 Digital Object(s); 39.6 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2017; UA003.010.00007; 17 Digital Object(s); 31.7 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2018; UA003.010.00008; 13 Digital Object(s); 21.6 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds files, 2018; UA003.010.00009; 18 Digital Object(s); 21.8 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2018-10-26; UA003.010.00010; 13 Digital Object(s); 31.52 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, special session, 2018-12-20; UA003.010.00011; 3 Digital Object(s); 13.17 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, in orientation session, 2019-01-16; UA003.010.00012; 2 Digital Object(s); 6.4 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2019-02-04; UA003.010.00013; 15 Digital Object(s); 23.44 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, special session, 2019-03-26; UA003.010.00014; 6 Digital Object(s); 17.04 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2019-05-06; UA003.010.00015; 10 Digital Object(s); 23.12 Megabytes
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2019 October 21; UA003.002324; 29.4 Megabytes 16 files
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2020 January 28; UA003.002364; 23.81 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2020 May 01; UA003.002365; 7.17 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2020 July 24; UA003.002366; 8.86 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee files, 2020 October 30; UA003.002367; 16.75 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
- Subject Files, 1889 -- 1990; UA003.011; 2.9 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials from different schools, projects, partnerships, and events at Tufts University that also may be documented elsewhere in the Trustees collection. This series maintains the original order of the subject files. Items include announcements, memoranda, letters, and reports dating from the early to late twentieth century. Items of interest include information about the Manpower Commission (1944) and WWII social policy. Other items include brief histories of the Dental School, Fletcher School, and Veterinary School.
  - AAUP, 1932 -- 1990; UA003.011.096.00001 (Box 96)
  - Academic Affairs, 1974 -- 1975; UA003.011.096.00002 (Box 96)
  - Agreements- miscellaneous, 1979 -- 1980; UA003.011.096.00003 (Box 96)
  - Alumni Association Bylaw Change, 1972 -- 1984; UA003.011.096.00004 (Box 96)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1979 -- 1981; UA003.011.096.00005 (Box 96)
  - Angell Memorial, 1984 -- 1990; UA003.011.096.00006 (Box 96)
  - Bylaws, 1924 -- 1986; UA003.011.096.00007 (Box 96)
  - China Project, 1986 -- 1987; UA003.011.096.00008 (Box 96)
  - Committee-Trustee/Admin./Fac./Carnegie Self-Study 59-63, 1960; UA003.011.096.00009 (Box 96)
  - Committee-Faculty adhoc- YRO, 1974; UA003.011.096.00010 (Box 96)
  - Contracts, Medical School, 1949 -- 1983; UA003.011.096.00011 (Box 96)
  - Dean Loew, 1981; UA003.011.096.00012 (Box 96)
  - Dental-accreditation, 1963 -- 1977; UA003.011.096.00013 (Box 96)
  - Dental-Bylaws, 1983 -- 1984; UA003.011.096.00014 (Box 96)
  - Dental-Clinics, 1987; UA003.011.096.00015 (Box 96)
  - Dental-Departments, 1966 -- 1970; UA003.011.096.00016 (Box 96)
  - Dental History, 1889 -- 1961; UA003.011.096.00017 (Box 96)
  - Dental-other, 1972 -- 1988; UA003.011.096.00018 (Box 96)
  - Diplomas, 1969 -- 1974; UA003.011.096.00019 (Box 96)
  - Dormitory Construction Bonds, 1959 -- 1965; UA003.011.096.00020 (Box 96)
  - Dormitory Indenture- Old Colony, 1960 -- 1968; UA003.011.096.00021 (Box 96)
  - Drugs, 1986; UA003.011.096.00022 (Box 96)
  - Educational Rights and Privacy Act/ Policy Statement, 1974 -- 1977; UA003.011.096.00023 (Box 96)
  - Emeriti Professors, 1964 -- 1974; UA003.011.096.00024 (Box 96)
  - Engineering-Departmets, 1972; UA003.011.096.00025 (Box 96)
  - Engineering Bylaws, 1968 -- 1982; UA003.011.096.00026 (Box 96)
  - Engineering, Accreditation, 1972; UA003.011.096.00027 (Box 96)
  - Enzyme Center 1990, UA003.011.096.00028 (Box 96)
  - Eppinger and Russell Co., Correspondence, 1932; UA003.011.096.00029 (Box 96)
  - Faculty-miscellaneous, 1974; UA003.011.096.00030 (Box 96)
  - Financial Aid, 1932 -- 1990; UA003.011.096.00031 (Box 96)
  - Financial Statements, 1932 -- 1990; UA003.011.096.00032 (Box 96)
  - Fletcher, Bylaws, 1932 -- 1990; UA003.011.096.00033 (Box 96)
  - Fletcher, History, 1932 -- 1990; UA003.011.096.00034 (Box 96)
  - Fletcher, miscellaneous, 1932 -- 1990; UA003.011.096.00035 (Box 96)
  - FSLD (Misc.), UA003.011.097.00001 (Box 97)
  - Fletcher, status as a division, 1955; UA003.011.097.00002 (Box 97)
  - Fletcher, Venezuela, UA003.011.097.00003 (Box 97)
  - Florida Mineral Rights, UA003.011.097.00004 (Box 97)
  - Florida investments, correspondence, 1928; UA003.011.097.00005 (Box 97)
  - Institutes, UA003.011.097.00006 (Box 97)
  - Liberal Arts-R.O.T.C., 1972; UA003.011.097.00007 (Box 97)
  - Mass: Corps and Taxation, 1969 -- 1970; UA003.011.097.00008 (Box 97)
  - Medford/Somerville, UA003.011.097.00009 (Box 97)
  - Medical-Faculty Appts., UA003.011.097.00010 (Box 97)
  - Medical-Bylaws, UA003.011.097.00011 (Box 97)
  - Medical-Admissions, UA003.011.097.00012 (Box 97)
  - Medical-Accreditation, UA003.011.097.00013 (Box 97)
  - OEO, UA003.011.097.00014 (Box 97)
  - Papers, Article, Misc. info, 1970 -- 1980; UA003.011.097.00015 (Box 97)
  - Personnel Policy Committee, UA003.011.097.00016 (Box 97)
  - Personnel Policy Committe, 4 Feb, 6 May, 23 June 1981, UA003.011.097.00017 (Box 97)
  - Questionnaires-Misc., UA003.011.097.00018 (Box 97)
  - Resources Committee, UA003.011.097.00019 (Box 97)
  - Resources-Misc., May 19, UA003.011.097.00020 (Box 97)
  - Resources Committee Bequests, 1953 -- 1979; UA003.011.097.00021 (Box 97)
  - R.O.T.C., UA003.011.097.00022 (Box 97)
  - Trustees-Jackson: Self-Study, 1967 -- 1980; UA003.011.097.00023 (Box 97)
  - Trustees-Report, 1984; UA003.011.097.00024 (Box 97)
  - Trustees-Letters of Resignation, 1962 -- 1965; UA003.011.097.00025 (Box 97)
  - Tufts Institutional Studies, part 1, UA003.011.097.00026 (Box 97)
  - Tufts Institutional Studies, part 2, UA003.011.097.00027 (Box 97)
  - TUSVM, UA003.011.097.00028 (Box 97)
  - Veterinary School #1 Letters, UA003.011.097.00029 (Box 97)
  - Veterinary School #2 Memos, UA003.011.097.00030 (Box 97)
  - Veterinary School #3 Contracts, UA003.011.098.00001 (Box 98)
  - Veterinary School #4 Reports, UA003.011.098.00002 (Box 98)
  - Veterinary School #5 Finances, UA003.011.098.00003 (Box 98)
  - Veterinary School #6 Media, UA003.011.098.00004 (Box 98)
  - Veterinary School #7 Misc., UA003.011.098.00005 (Box 98)
  - Veterinary School #8 Accreditation Report, UA003.011.098.00006 (Box 98)
- Board of Visitors Committee, 1900 -- 1978; UA003.012; 1.7 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials from the Board of Visitors Committee from 1888 to 1970. Folders contain agendas, minutes, and letters from members of the committee. Items include correspondence from trustees who have observed classes, focusing on their impressions of the faculty and the quality of classes.
  - Benefactors: William H. Ryder Estate, UA003.012.034.00001 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: Scott Estate, UA003.012.034.00002 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: Smith Estate, UA003.012.034.00003 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: Rosa Smith Estate, UA003.012.034.00004 (Box 34)